Rodolfo Muñoz

91/6 Giles Street, EH6 6BZ, Edinburgh

+44(0)7948292189

rodolfo@rodolfomunoz.com

github.com/rodolfo-munoz

A responsible, enthusiastic, and proficient IT undergraduate with an ability to quickly learn and master new technologies and challenges. Holds a broad range of skills including system design and implementation, programming languages, networks, web development, and troubleshooting. Reliable, punctual, and able to work equally well within teams or individually, demonstrating resourcefulness and determination when presented with new projects or problems to resolve. In the final year of his studies and keen to apply his learnt skills to real life application, gaining further experience in a practical setting.

Key Skills

- Web Applications
- > Python / Django > HTML 5 > CSS3
- CSS3
- JavaScript / jQuery

- Git / GitHub
 SQL / SQLite
 OS Troubleshooting
 REST APIs, JSON
 Networking
 Hardware
 Troubleshooting
 Programming
 System Design
 System Assembly

Education

Computing and Information Technology (BSc) **Open University**

2016-Present (Exp. 2021)

In the final year of studies with 300 credits earned and expecting to complete this course with Honours. Projected classification: First class. This is a comprehensive course covering a wide range of areas including:

- Technologies in practice
 - Microsoft networking essentials
 - Linux
- Web development
 - Web applications (Cordova)
 - o HTML 5 and CSS3
 - JavaScript
 - Bootstrap
 - o PHP
 - o SQL
 - Python / Django
- Object-oriented Java programming (Java and Python)
- Cisco networking CCNA
- Algorithms, data structures and computability (with Python)
- Data Management and Analysis (Using Jupyter Notebooks, Pandas and NumPy)
- Mobile and Cloud Technologies

- MySQL Level 1
- PHP Level 1
- JQuery Level 1
- JavaScript Level 1
- CSS3 Level 1
- HTML5 Level 1

Cisco Certified Entry Level Technician (CCENT)

2019

- Validated skills to install, manage, maintain, and troubleshoot a small enterprise branch network, including network security.
- Currently working towards CCNA certification

Cisco Networking Academy Program courses

2018-2019

- Introduction to networks
- Routing and switching essentials
- Scaling Networks
- Connecting networks

All courses passed with merit

Employment

Chef de Partie – Roseleaf Ltd., Edinburgh.

2014 - Present

- Overseeing operations in a section of the kitchen, ensuring cooperation and coordination between food stations and proper execution of individual dishes
- Food prep and cooking
- Knowing and following food safety guidelines
- Cleaning, organizing workstation and Maintaining equipment

Chef de Partie – Whighams Wine Cellars, Edinburgh.

2013 - 2014

- Food prep and cooking
- Knowing and following food safety guidelines
- Cleaning, organizing workstation and Maintaining equipment

Chef de Partie – Amarone Restaurant, Edinburgh.

2012 - 2013

• Responsible for the Pasta and sauce sections. Amarone is situated in the heart of Edinburgh Newtown, catering for up to 450 covers.

Head Chef - New Albert's, Marbella

2010 - 2012

Chef de Partie - Charme Restaurant, Marbella, Spain

2008 - 2010

Waiter - Club La Costa, Fuengirola, Spain

2006 - 2008

Desktop Support – Sicograf (Argentina)

2000 - 2005

- Sicograf was a Toshiba authorised dealer and repair centre.
- Desktop support of Toshiba equipment, printers, and photocopiers.
- Walking customers through installing applications and computer peripherals

- Asking targeted questions to diagnose problems
- Conduct remote troubleshooting
- Record technical issues and solutions in logs
- Follow up with clients to ensure their systems are functional

Personal

- Right to work
- Excellent English and Native Spanish skills both written and spoken
- Conversational Italian